So in the real estate brokerage world, when you get your
real estate license, typically you're taught to just do one thing.
You're taught to just be a listing agent. You're taught to
just do residential. You're taught to just be a buyer's agent.
You're taught to only do commercial, to not do residential,
to not worry about investing in real estate, to not wholesale.
And so what we call everybody with us here at TRE is
entrepreneurs, because we feel that you should be a true real estate professional
and not just limit yourself to one thing, right?
Because if the market shifts, if you don't know how to do this or that, then
you're going to be limited in how much money you can make and how successful you'll be.
So we teach all of our entrepreneurs how to make money in and
on real estate and how to make money in every aspect of real estate.